

CONTACT



01741-236957



debdipon37@gmail.com



Moulvibazar, Sylhet, Bangladesh

SKILL:

- Computer Basic
- Computer Graphics
- Web Design
- Web Development
- > Python Development
- > C# Development

LANGUAGE:

- Bangla
- English
- > Hindi

Clearance:

- > Police report clearable
- Blood group report o+
- Medical report clearable

DIPON DEB

GRAPHICS DESIGNER

EDUCATION:

Ajamoni Multiletter High School, Moulvibazar 2019-2020

(SSC) Secondary School Certificate obtained. Getting 4.94 out of 5. (Subject- Science)

Moulvibazar Politechnic Institute, Moulvibazar

2020 - running

Diploma in Computer Science

Summary:

Hello! My name is Dipon Deb, i'am from Bangladesh. I have more then 1 years experience in graphic design like as Business card, Brochure, Tri Fold Brochure, Background Remove, Post Design, Flyer, Illustration, cv, Application, Letter, Photoshop editing and Logo design. I can bring fresh ideas in order to creative visuals solutions to communicate various messages. Thank you.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Kamalpur Union, Moulvibazar

January 2021- March 2022

Responsibility:

- Teaching Basic Computer
- Microsoft Office
- Graphics Design

Future Group, Moulvibazar

March 2021- September 2022

Responsibility:

- ❖ Teaching Basic Computer
- Microsoft Office
- Graphics Design

OTHERS CERTIFICATION:

- Traning Microsoft Office "Bangladesh Computer College"-(BCC), Moulvibazar
- Traning Grapics Design "We For Bangladesh", Moulvibazar Municipality, Moulvibazar